buo s yes s I'm stupid you were blocking
buo s si s soy tonta estabas bloqueando
people who were telling you in the
a gente que te estaba diciendo en el
chat where the 240 bucks were that you should have
chat que dónde estaban los 240 pavos que
donated to the association
tenías que haber donado a la asociación
against cancer climb I hope you're
contra el cáncer trepa Espero que estéis
aware of these messages and
al loro de estos de estos mensajes y
directly the
directamente los
[Music]
[Música]
neither the other nor the other and so 15 days 15
ni el otro ni el otro y así 15 días 15
days that you have passed and you still have not
días que has pasado y todavía no has
given explanations and she told me that
dado explicaciones y me ha dicho que
Peppa showed up today at 10 in
Peppa se ha presentado hoy a las 10 de
the morning to make a donation of 240 the
la mañana pas hacer una donación de 240
strongest thing is that apparently when they
lo más fuerte es que por lo visto cuando
gave her the paper of the
le han dado el papel de la ley de
data protection law it turns out that pppa
protección de datos resulta que pppa
asked that this donation not be
pedido que esa donación no se no sea
public because what she was
pública porque ella lo que estaba
waiting for was to see if somehow she
esperando es a ver si de alguna forma se
could change that date And show it that
podía cambiar esa fecha Y enseñarlo ese
Monday and she had done it that Monday and I
lunes y lo había hecho ese lunes y yo lo
know who because of this I am
sé quién por yo esto soy
[Music]
[Música]
stupid let's listen to it carefully because
tonta vamos a escucharlo bien porque
this has more behind it than yesterday it
esto tiene más detrás que ayer se nos
went unnoticed he says it Javi
pasó desapercibido lo dice el el Javi
Oliveira No no well indi damned illo
oliveira No no pues indi condenad illo
never Nor  ar de Troya neither Loli Huerta nor
nunca Ni ar de Troya ni Loli Huerta ni
I have spoken badly of Antonio David
yo hemos hablado mal de de Antonio David
on the contrary the only thing that burns Troy
al contrario lo único que arde Troya
was very angry because When
estaba muy enfadado porque Cuando entró
Antonio David came in here to greet my mom and
Antonio David aquí a saludar a mi mamá y
to surprise her through
a darle la sorpresa por mediación de
Lolly wert I have always said and I will say it he
Lolly wert siempre he dicho y lo diré
said eh One day I'm going to take you to my
dijo eh Un día os voy a llevar a mi
channel nca due to circumstances for whatever it
canal nca por circunstancias por lo que
is I don't care due to circumstances
sea a mí me da igual por circunstancias
or for whatever because you don't talk
o por lo que sea porque no os habláis
to him they are not of the greatest importance Ah it is
con él no tienen la mayor importancia Ah
not of the greatest importance Eh well let's
no tiene la mayor importancia Eh bueno a
see so as not to have the greatest importance
ver para no tener la mayor importancia
climb I'm going to remind you of something that
trepa te voy a recordar yo una cosa que
I have around here and since I no longer
tengo yo por aquí y como yo ya no me la
take her So we use the way
llevo Entonces utilizamos la vía por
because since she's a fan you know we use
porque como ella es fan sabes utilizamos
the way we say things to see if he
la vía le decimos cosas a ver si él
can get her to leave Peppa Antonio
puede conseguir que deje a Peppa Antonio
or whoever what I'm saying I already
o a quien a mí lo que voy diciendo Yo ya
suspected that something was going on
sospechaba que algo estaba pasando
because Antonio David no no I'm not going to say he
porque Antonio David no no voy a decir
promised us he invited us he said something like
nos prometió nos invitó dijo algo así
one day one day of this like this I will
como un día un día de esto así os
take you to my channel you know everything that
llevaré a mi canal ya sabéis todo lo que
means Antony David takes you to his
supone que Antony David te lleve a su
channel thousands of people are watching you
canal miles de personas te están viendo
thousands of people can subscribe to
miles de personas se pueden suscribir a
your channel and you can get a boost
tu canal y puedes pegar un subidón lo
just like Oliveira Juan got
mismo que le ha pegado oliveira Juan
juus FJ soft clear Amparo Enrique
juus FJ blando claro Amparo Enrique
García and all those who have passed by and
García y todos los que han pasado y han
collaborated with Antonio David that
colaborado con Antonio David ese un
sweet thing doesn't upset anyone else when you
dulce no amarga a nadie más cuando tú
're making a daily defense of
estás haciendo una defensa diaria de
Antonio David his family and his cause t
Antonio David su familia y su causa t
fist here what he just said is a
fist aquí lo que acaba de decir es un
sweet thing that doesn't upset anyone because if
dulce que no amarga a nadie porque si
Antonio David takes his channel you have
Antonio David te lleva su canal tienes
the possibility of being seen by thousands of
la posibilidad de que te vean miles de
people but more so when we are
personas pero más cuando estamos
defending the cause What a Trojan cause
defendiendo la causa Qué causa de Troya
What a cause if when your Sunday comes around we're
Qué causa si cuando te toque tu domingo
going to see that you didn't even know Antonio
vamos a ver que tú ni conocías a Antonio
David and when you met him you were putting him
David y cuando lo conociste lo pusiste
down but you and the climb if there's another
verde pero tú y la trepa si hay otro
reason apart from the money why you
motivo aparte del dinero por el que os
approached Loli it was to get
acercaste a la Loli era para conseguir
collaborations with Antonio David because
colaboraciones con Antonio David porque
there you believed that you were going to
ahí se creíais ustedes que os ibais a
become famous on YouTube I knew that something
ser famosos en YouTube sabía que algo
was happening and from
estaba pasando y por la experiencia de
Antonio David's experience it doesn't surprise me at all that he
Antonio David no me extraña nada que
went from being a YouTuber and only takes his channel
pasara de youtuber y solo lleva su canal
to Twitter people who are on Twitter the
a Twitter gente que está en Twitter los
collaborators who are with  he is a
colaboradores que están con él son gente
Twitter person but I knew that something
de Twitter pero yo sabía que algo por
why does Antonio David not keep his word and
qué no cumple Antonio David su palabra y
not on his channel I asked myself this is the
no ha su canal yo me lo pregunt est la
first time I'm doing this
primera vez que lo estoy haciendo esta
reflection or this thought live
reflexión o este pensamiento en directo
Why doesn't Antonio David invite us to
Por qué Antonio David no nos invita a
pppa and me what has happened while
pppa y ami qué ha pasado mientras
also During this time they put us in
también Durante este tiempo nos meten en
a war where Peppa does not have to be
una guerra donde Peppa no se tiene que
defending herself I have to be defending myself
estar defendiendo yo me tengo que estar
and if I know I do not come she has to be
defendiendo y si lo se no vengo se tiene
defending herself from different
que estar defendiendo de diferentes
attacks and different stories
ataques y de diferentes historias
Antonio David does not collaborate with you
Antonio David no colabora con ustedes
because neither are you friends of Antonio
porque ni ustedes sois amigos de Antonio
David nor Antonio David is a friend of yours there is the one in the
David ni Antonio David es amigo vuestro
middle the one in the
hay la que está por medio la que está
middle and without more there is no type
por medio y sin más no hay ningún tipo
of relationship nor should you defend the
de relación ni habéis de defendió la
cause nor does he know you nor do
causa ni él los conoce a ustedes ni
you know him and within his pride he said
ustedes a él y dentro de su orgullo dijo
Well if now he tells me to go I wouldn't go
Pues si ahora me dice a mí de ir no iría
and I say what nonsense No that's the only thing
y digo qué tontería No eso es lo único
but I have never listened to the
pero yo nunca le he escuchado a la
truth I no I am not like him I am not
verdad yo no yo no soy como él yo no me
going to make up a lie I am not going
voy a inventar una mentira yo no me voy
to make up a lie well that thing that
a inventar una mentira bueno eso de que
you are not going to make up a lie climber
no te vas a inventar una mentira trepa
is very  simple with tweezers to give you an
está mu cillo con pinza por ponerte un
example So the one that comes to mind
ejemplo Así que se me viene a la cabeza
but let's go a random example Uh well
pero vamos un ejemplo cualquiera Eh pues
two days ago I called him and I sent him
hace dos días que yo lo llamo y le mando
WhatsApp A few days ago and I sent him
WhatsApp Hace unos días y le mando
WhatsApp Ah I give you permission you give me
WhatsApp Ah te doy permiso me das
permission to put the calls
permiso para que pongas las llamadas
from when you and I didn't talk you give me
desde cuando tú y yo no hablamos me das
permission to put the calls from
permiso para que ponga las llamadas de
when she and I didn't talk permission
cuando ella y yo no hablamos permiso
for her conversations putting
para las conversaciones de ella poniendo
Loli green saying that she's going to
verde a la Loli diciendo que la va
pluck her that didn't give me but here she gives me
desplumar ese no me daba pero aquí me da
permission to prove that she's been
permiso para que yo demuestre que ella
trying to contact me For
ha estado intentando contactarme Durante
the last few months neither I call you nor
los últimos meses ni yo te llamo a ti ni
you call me or anything at all You're
tú me llamas a mí ni nada de nada Eres
a liar if
un mentiroso si
that's you're a
eso eres un
liar if it's not for me if it's not for
Mentiroso si no es por mí si no es por
me then I'll take it as the alluded to just in
mí pues yo me doy por la aludida por si
case okay what do you think it's for
acaso vale ustedes qué cree que es por
me nothing at all well since she
mí nada de nada pues bueno ya como me
gave me permission She says this nothing at all in
dio permiso Dice esto nada de nada en
August while I was getting green green
agosto mientras me estaba poniendo verde
yellow blue August called me
verde amarillo azulón agosto me habló
to let me know that I was appearing
para avisarme de que yo estaba saliendo
on the TR antenna you know that I have to
en la antena TR sabes que me tengo que
find out by  she that I'm on
enterar yo por ella de que estoy en
Antena 3 leave me alone here You're not going to come
Antena 3 dejarme en paz aquí No vais a
back any of you like you said Peppa I
volver ninguno cómo habías dicho Peppa
forgot that's the only thing but
que se me olvidaba eso es lo único pero
I've never listened to the truth I
yo nunca le he escuchado a la verdad yo
'm not like him I'm not going to make up
no soy como él yo no me voy a inventar
a lie I'm not going to make up a
una mentira yo no me voy a inventar una
lie last night without going any further you said
mentira anoche sin ir más lejos dijiste
the following Listen to him and another one on ard
lo siguiente Escúchalo y a otra en ard
Troya Nesa is telling me that they took
Troya me está diciendo Nesa que sacaron
a photo of my mother what scoundrels
una foto de mi madre qué sinvergüenzas
you're acting like the one you found out
te estás haciendo como la que te enteras
today that the one from Troya took a photo of
hoy de que al de Troya sacó una foto de
your mother because you according to ard de Troya and
tu madre porque tú según ard de Troya y
recognized by you sent a photo of
reconocido por ti mandaste una foto de
your mother to say I don't have money I don't
tu madre para decir no tengo dinero no
even have enough for a bottle of water and my
tengo ni para una botellita de agua y mi
mother is thirsty to ask Loli
madre tiene sed para pedirle a la Loli
this is today in the same live where you
esto es hoy en el mismo directo donde
say you don't make up lies What a
dices que no te inventas mentiras Qué
scoundrel has
sinvergüenza
life
ha vida
Look at the truth he's telling me saying
Mira verdad me está diciendo diendo el
Antonio live yesterday took the photo of
Antonio en directo de ayer sacó la foto
you and your mother well wow he just found
tuya y de tu mamá bueno vaya se acaba de
out live But climb if you
enterar en directo Pero trepa si tú te
just found out live  How is it that
acabas de enterar en directo Cómo es que
the day before you said this I have enough for
el día anterior dijiste esto tengo para
a bottle of water They brought like
una botella de agua Ho han traído como
two boxes of meat I have enough for water I have and
dos cajas carne tengo para agua tengo y
the water is useful How is it that you answered
el agua serv Cómo es que has contestado
about the water the day before finding out
a lo del agua el día antes de enterarte
climb this will not be a little lie that you
trepa esto no será una mentirilla que te
made up like a c word that you say out of your
has inventado como c palabra que sueltas
mouth but how can those
por la boca pero cómo pueden es esas
Minds For example, I read that last
Mentes Por ejemplo yo es que le hoy
night that you had a plot
anoche decir eso que teníais una trama
between the three of you and how not you didn't get more
entre los tres y cóm no no subías de
Followers that it was impossible that you had
Seguidores que era imposible que tenías
13 in that one that you didn't reach 4000 and
13 en en el ese que no llegabas a 4000 y
and I say me and the one who has 140 and something and
y digo yo y el que tiene 140 y tanto y
has 2000 people where are these people
tiene 2000 personas dónde estáa gente
has 146000 and has the maximum that reaches
tiene 146000 y tiene lo máximo que llega
but you still have almost 4000 and you
pero todavía tú tienes casi 4000 y
have 13 people clone the truth is that
tienes 13 personas clón la verdad es que
the channel is going very bad eh look that you have
el canal va muy mal eh mira que tenés
140,000 subscribers and there are not
140.000 suscriptores y que no haya
140,000 people live come on, I have
140.000 personas en directo vamos yo es
not seen that from anyone eh I
que eso no se lo he visto a nadie eh yo
see Diego  arabal with 150,000 and has
veo a Diego arabal con 150.000 y tiene
150,000 viewers
150.00 espect
in the live shows I see Juanjo with
en los directos yo veo a Juanjo con
500,000 subscribers and he has 500,000
500000 suscriptores y tiene 500000
viewers in each live show it's the most
espectadores en cada directo es lo más
normal thing in the world of all God's life
normal del mundo de toda la vida de Dios
it's like that let's go it's that 2 + 2 Are 240 that's how
es así vamos es que 2+ 2 Son 240 es que
it works but well here the
eso funciona así pero bueno aquí la
plot is the following deos listen to
trama es la siguiente deos a escuchar
this says jav oliveira no no
esto lo dice jav oliveira no no
well conillo never Neither Troya burns nor LoL
pues conillo nunca Ni arde Troya ni LoL
and we have spoken
y hemos hablado
davar trying to deny the climber because
davar intentando negar la trepa porque
surely you will not have caught her and it's
seguramente no la habréis pillado y es
something that escaped us yesterday It is that the
algo que se nos escapó ayer Es que la
climber insinuated in her live show yesterday that
trepa insinuó en su directo de ayer que
Troya burns probably has
arde Troya probablemente tenga grabada
a recorded conversation where the three of them are
una conversación donde los tres están
criticizing Antonio David Of course in
criticando a Antonio David Claro en el
case that is true Who do you
caso de que eso sea cierto A quién
think it affects because I think that
creéis que le afecta porque yo creo que
Peppa with the little shame that she has that she does not care if they bring
a Peppa con la poca vergüenza que tiene
up the
que la ha da igual que saquen lo del
cancer thing, if they bring up a conversation
cáncer que le saquen una conversación
putting it green Antonio David she brings it to the
poniendo verd Antonio David se la trae
pyro she only wants  tiki tiki
al piro ella nada más que quiere tiki
to ard de Troya he does
tiki a ard de Troya le da lo mismo ard
n't care ard de Troya doesn't know Antonio there was
de Troya no conoce Antonio había
absolutely nothing nor has any
absolutamente De nada ni tiene ningún
kind of contact with him In case he
tipo de contacto con él En el caso de
has ard Troya to a
que tenga ard Troya a una conversación
recorded conversation or the climber has a
grabada o la trepa tenga una
recorded conversation where they speak ill of
conversación grabada donde hablan mal de
Antonio David who gives him a little bit of a
Antonio David a quien le da un poquillo
thing is Loli of course and says climber
de cosilla es a Loli claro y dice trepa
that that is a lie that she has not
que eso es mentira que eso ella no lo ha
said that that is a lie that I have already
dicho que eso es una mentira que yo me
said it the day that she
he inventado ya lo dije el día que ella
did the Well she also did a survey
hizo el Bueno también hizo una encuesta
No what do you think who I go with with
No qué os parece con quién voy con
Antonio or with Pepe I found it disgusting
Antonio o con Pepe me pareció asquerosa
someone told him and
alguien se lo dijo y Se bloqueó todo el
everyone who contradicts him was blocked but not
mundo que le lleve la contraria pero no
the contrary is what in an opinion no
la contraria es lo que en una opinión no
no you have to dance to her don't
no a ella hay que bailarle el agua no me
tell me climber don't tell me more that Loli
digas trepa no me digas más que la Loli
Huerta has the audacity to ban from her
Huerta tiene la osadía de banear de su
chat anyone who says something that does
chat a todo el que diga algo que a ella
not interest her come on I can't
no le interesa vamos no me lo puedo yo
believe it So Lolly Huerta has
de creer O sea que la Lolly Huerta tiene
the nerve according to you to block
el morro según tú de bloquear a
anyone who says something that  she's not
cualquiera que diga algo que a ella no
interested I hope you're aware of these
le interesa Espero que estéis al loro de
messages and directly
estos de estos mensajes y directamente
those
los
who should have donated to the
que tenía que haber donado a la
association against cancer climbs I hope
asociación contra el cáncer trepa Espero
you're aware of these
que estéis al loro de estos de estos
messages and directly block them I
mensajes y directamente los bloque hais
don't want I don't want these people here
no quiero no quiero a esta gente aquí
Today I don't want these people here today to the
Hoy no quiero a esta gente aquí hoy a la
people who are asking you what you have
gente que te está preguntando que qué
done with the money that was raised
has hecho con el dinero que se recaudó
live you don't want these people
en directo que no quieres a esta gente
today but well not today nor tomorrow nor the day
hoy pero bueno ni hoy ni mañana ni
after nor the other nor the other nor the other
pasado ni el otro ni el otro ni el otro
and so on 15 days and she told me that Peppa
y así 15 días y me ha dicho que Peppa se
showed up today at 10 in the morning
ha presentado hoy a las 10 de la mañana
to make a donation of 200 40 or so
para hacer una donación de 200 40 o sea
this morning she showed up to
esta mañana se ha presentado ella para
make the donation suddenly this morning
hacer La donación de repente esta mañana
coincidentally was the day that she was
casualmente era el día en el que ella
going to donate it effectively this morning
iba a donarlo efectivamente esta mañana
at 10 she went and donated 240 the
a las 10 ha cogido y ha donado 240 lo
strongest thing is that apparently when they
más fuerte es que por lo visto cuando le
gave her the paper of the
han dado el papel de la ley de
data protection law Because when it
protección de datos Porque cuando
exceeds 100 you have to sign it
sobrepasa los 100 tienes que firmarlo
because they have to pass it to the Treasury it
porque lo tienen que pasar a Hacienda
turns out that Peppa  asked that this
resulta que Peppa pedido que esa
donation not be published so that the
donación no sea publicado que la
association cannot say whether he has donated or
asociación no pueda decir si ha donado o
not and has asked him to sign a paper for
no y le ha pedido firmado un papel para
that and the girl from the association has
eso y la chica de la asociación le ha
told him that that cannot be done that she
dicho que eso no se puede hacer quera
wanted it to be no, I mean
quería que fuera no
she wanted the receipt not the
o sea quería ella el el recibo no el
proof of having donated but that it not
justificante de haber donado pero que no
be public I imagine so that
fuera público me imagino para que no se
the date could not be seen no indeed That's how it
viera la fecha no efectivamente Así
looks 15 days that you have
tiene toda la pinta 15 días que has
passed and you still have not given
pasado y todavía no has dado
explanations you have given explanations for
explicaciones has dado explicaciones de
everything except that look at how the
todo menos de eso fíjate tú cómo son la
thing is that you are answering me now that
cosa que me estás contestando ahora a
last night we said that you insinuated that you
que anoche dijimos que insinuaste que
had a conversation with Loli
teníais una conversación de la Loli
speaking badly of Antonio David I mean you are going
hablando mal de Antonio David o sea vas
to answer everything except Where
a contestar a todo menos que A dónde
is the money what is it that we want to
está la pasta qué es lo que queremos
know to us the rest of this
saber a nosotros el resto de tontería
climber nonsense does not matter to us because what she
trepa nos importa poco porque ella lo
was wondering about was to see if in
que estaba esando es a a ver si de
some way that date could be changed
alguna forma se podía cambiar esa fecha
And show it that Monday and she had done it
Y enseñarlo ese lunes y lo había hecho
that Monday and I know who
ese lunes y yo lo sé qui
because I was
por estuve
talking just when the live of the person on
hablando justo cuando empezó el directo
stage started and it was just when he started
del del esceo y fue justo cuando empezó
ranting camos  and she opened the live
a despotricar camos y abrió el directo
saying that she wasn't showing it anymore and she
diciendo que ya no lo enseñaba y ella
was waiting for someone to come
estaba esperando a que viniera alguien
if she could change change a date and
si podía cambiarse cambiar una fecha y
do it herself when I realized m Hey don't
hacerlo ella cuando me di a m Oye no me
touch my balls I tell her Hey don't
toques los [__] yo le digo Oye no te
touch your balls no don't you touch them
toque los [__] no no me los toques tú
to me u u no she can't take it anymore she
a mí u u no ya no lo aguanta eso ella
needs a suck-ass and I've
necesita un chupac culo y yo no lo he
never been one climber that you would be a suck-ass
nunca trepa que tú serías chupac culo
who would think climber that you would be a
quién pensaría trepa que tú serías
suck-ass come on it's that I won't be the one who
chupac culo vamos es que no seré yo
dares to even imagine it
quien me atreva ni siquiera a imaginarlo
and much less with someone who opens your
y mucho menos con alguien que te abra el
wallet Loli that I love you I haven't
monedero Loli que te quiero yo no he
done that yes I do love her I tell her
hecho eso sí Yo sí la quiero se lo digo
every day clo aren't you going to love her I
a diario clo no la vas a querer se lo
tell her every day that I love you Loli that I
digo a diario que te quiero Loli que te
love you I remind you every day so you do
quiero te lo recuerdo a diario para que
n't forget Loli how have you done it
no se te olvide a Loli cómo has hecho tú
every day to Loli that I love you I haven't
a diario a Loli que te quiero yo no he
done that I know I do love her I
hecho eso yo s yo sí la quiero se lo
tell her every day clo aren't you going to love her Oh I
digo a diario clo no la vas a querer Ay
love you we have to take care of the plants we have to take
que te quiero hay que cuidar las plantas
care of the plants that don't grow by themselves
hay que cuidar las plantas que no crecen
Eh  you have to take care of them but without
solas Eh hay que cuidarlas pero sin
flattery eh you just remind her
peloteo eh simplemente tú le recuerdas
every day that you love them daily
todos los días que las quieres a diario
without flattery and that's it January 24,
sin peloteo y ya está 24 de enero del
2022 you have a Peppa channel I'm going to be
2022 tienes canal Peppa voy a ser de
different Loli is officially
otra manera Loli es oficialmente
adopted by this great community
adoptada por esta gran comunidad
well it has me look at the hairs standing on end
bien me tiene mirate los vellos de punta
the hairs standing on end you have me Loli what would I
los vellos de punta me tienes Loli qué
say to Loli that day that had her so
le diría a Loli ese día que la tenía tan
excited with the hairs standing on end don't you
emocionada con los vellos de punta no te
remember when you thought that
acuerdas cuando tú pensabas que que
Antonio was there and I told you yes already like
Antonio estaba y yo te dije si ya como
vast Antonio recording the calls of
vast Antonio grabando las llamadas de
the three with all the things that were said And about
los tres con la de cosas que se decían Y
whom it was said about whom it was said
de quién se decía de quién se decía
betweenpa Or does Antonio have recorded
entrepa O sea que Antonio tiene grabadas
calls where you affirm because you
llamadas donde tú afirmas porque lo
affirm it This is not an assumption you
afirmas Esto no es un supuesto lo
affirm it with all the things that were said And
afirmas con la de cosas que se decían Y
about whom it was said I don't know anymore maybe he
de quién se decían yo ya no lo sé a lo
scared her like this I don't
mejor le acojonado así de esta manera No
know Ah that Antonio could have
lo sé Ah que Antonio podría haberla
scared her like that maybe he
acojonado con esa manera lo mejor le
scared her like this I don't know
acojonado así de esta manera No lo sé
because it seems to me that with this insinuation
pues me da a mí que con esta insinuación
the box has  scared someone is you what's
la caja ha acojonado a alguien eres tú
good that with the community that has
lo que bueno que con la comunidad que se
stayed the truth is that your mother
ha quedado la verdad es que tu madre me
has done me a favor because she has taken
ha hecho un favor porque se ha llevado
a small group that I did not know were of
un grupito que yo no sabía que eran de
that ilk I had no idea and it
esa calaña yo no tenía ni idea y me
seems perfect to me that she has taken her and they have
parece perfecto que se la haya llevado y
stayed there with her now that
se hayan quedado allí con ella ahora que
she locks herself up official announcement today is
se encierre anuncio oficial hoy es el
Peppa Beltrán's last day on this
último día de Peppa Beltrán en este
channel I don't care what she does or what the
canal me da igual lo que haga ni lo que
blonde lady does or what
haga la la señora rubia ni lo que haga
any of them does I don't care here it
ninguno de ellos me da igual aquí se
puts an end to the climber Beltrán I
pone punto y final a la trepa Beltrán O
mean the one from Troy let's see if I get this straight
sea al de Troya a ver si yo me aclaro
because the truth is that I'm making a
porque la verdad es que esto me hago yo
mess of this eh In this episode I'm getting
un lío eh En este episodio me estoy
a little confused or so you
liando un poco o sea que tú consigues
finally manage after so many years
por fin después de tantos años
trying playing this key and
intentándolo tocando esta tecla y
playing the other you manage to have
tocando la otra consigues tener cada
almost 1000 viewers every night some
noche casi 1000 espectadores alguna
even more than 1000 viewers
incluso más de 1000 espectadores
criticizing the climber and that you
poniendo verde a la trepa y que tú De
Suddenly overnight when you
repente de la noche a la mañana cuando
have her who has not shut up
la tienes a ella que no se ha callado
because today she has not shut up You  you
porque que hoy no se ha callado Tú
launch an official announcement damaging
lanzas un anuncio oficial perjudicando
your YouTube business with which you
tu negocio de Youtube con el que
intend to stay because you quit your
pretendes mantenerte porque has dejado
job suddenly But
el trabajo de buenas a primeras Pero por
why when You were walking with the knife in your
qué cuando Ibas con el cuchillo en la
mouth without fear how is it that you Suddenly
boca sin miedo cómo es que tú De repente
you are born this afternoon not to say anything else
te naces esta tarde no decir más nada
How is it that it's over and you come back today to
Cómo que se ha acabado y vuelves hoy a
do a live against the flight
hacer un directo en contra del vuelo
are you scared of what If you are not
estás acojonado de qué Si tú no tienes
afraid If you have everything could it be that you have
miedo Si tú tienes de todo no será que
sacrificed this part of your business
has sacrificado esta parte de tu negocio
just in case another part is damaged
por si acaso se te perjudica otra parte
I ask eh I ask open I would not
pregunto eh pregunto hbre yo no
sacrifice and I would stop
sacrificaría y dejaría por toda la cara
talking about a topic that is giving me
de hablar de un tema que me está dando
money and views every night could it
todas las noches un dinero y unas
be that there is a third
visitas no será que hay una tercera
person What did he tell you Shut up Since I do
persona Qué te ha dicho Cállate Ya que
n't want this to be thrown around here
no quiero que esto se tire por aquí
Shut up Take it, take it Shut up Shut up
Cállate Ya toma toma Cállate
my love I want to dance with you
Ya calla mi amor quiero bailar contigo
Seville
Sevilla
or eh Ah Zaragoza What a turkey I want to dance
o eh Ah Zaragoza Qué pavo quiero bailar
with you it's funny to me that people who
contigo me hace gracia que gente que
support the "I rebel" are harassing a
apoya el yo me revelo esté acosando una
woman at the levels that they are
mujer a los niveles que te están
harassing you Eh
acosando a ti Eh
then Calm down calm down everything will have
entonces Tranquila tranquila todo tendrá
its moment you will prove what  you want to
su momento tú demostrarás lo que quieras
prove and where you have to
demostrar y donde lo tengas que
prove it you have to prove it on the
demostrar lo tiene que demostrar en
internet what the hell is this
internet qué [__] está justificando esta
lady justifying What is this defending
señora Qué es lo que está defendiendo
This is also a moderator of
esta esta Esta es moderadora también de
Antonio David and this fight against
Antonio David y esta lucha contra las
injustices where is she going to have to
injusticias dónde va a tener que
justify money that she has collected in
justificar un dinero que ha cogido en
donations in a YouTube live well she
donaciones en un directo de YouTube pues
has to justify it
lo tiene que justificar públicamente
publicly publicly and no longer when she wants it is already
públicamente y ya no cuando quiera ya va
two weeks late Maribel García Good
tarde dos semanas Maribel García Buenas
afternoon ignorance speaks
tardes la ignorancia habla la
intelligence is silent Kisses to all Maribel
inteligencia calla Besos a todos Maribel
García Thank you very much sweetheart for those 5
García Muchas gracias corazón por esos 5
euros of Super chat that
eur de Super chat que
I go that of asking for super chat eh
yo vamos eso de pedir super chat eh
membership and things like that
membresía y cosas de esas
guind The condemned one is the one who does it I
guind El condenado es el que lo hace yo
don't have to do it I have already sent him
no tengo que hacerlo le he mandado ya un
a letter so that he gives me permission so that I
la carta para que me dé permiso para yo
can say that you can subscribe to
poder decir que os podéis suscribir
things like that whatever thing that
cosas de esas vayase cosa que que le
feels bad to him he just said that she doesn't
siente mal acaba de decir que ella no
ask he just said that she doesn't ask and it turns
pide acaba de decir que ella no pide y
out that I want to give
resulta que le que le iba yo quiero
m Alberto a gift because the
hacerle a m Alberto un regalo porque los
other day We were seeing lights for go and
otros dí Estuvimos viendo luces par va y
now the fan is broken one of
ahora se estopeado el ventilador uno de
the fans has the air
los ventiladores tiene el aire
conditioning has two fans
acondicionado tiene dos ventiladores
but the one in the center  it's broken and I
pero el del centro se la ha estropeado y
say look I'm going to get a bizum because
digo mira me voy a poner un bizum porque
I don't have the budget to buy him
no me llega el presupuesto de comprarle
what we saw he likes it's
lo que lo que vimos a él le gusta que es
a big ceiling light with some lights and
un un plafón grande con unas luces y
inside it has the
dentro tiene el las aspas de del
microwave blades I was going to say Oh what a case I'm
microonde iba a decir Ay qué caso estoy
terrible eh Well then that's what I was going to do I
fatal eh Bueno pues eso le iba a hacer
wanted to give him the gift there Alberto and
le quería hacer el regalo aí Alberto y
him and come on honey Look Alfonso Now
le y por vamos cariño Mira Alfonso Ahora
when you can bring me some cardboard a
cuando puedas tráeme un una cartulina un
some paper of those that I'm going to write down the Vu to
un papel de eso que vo a apuntar el Vu a
see if someone can help me buy him the
ver si alguien me ayuda a comprarle el
gift
regalo
at least for 1 because I have
a aunque sea 1 porque es que tengo
illusions that are very good and I can't get it it's not enough for me it's not
ilusiones que es muy bueno y no me llega
enough for him Why doesn't
no me llega no le llega Por qué no tiene
this lady have money for a fan?
para un ventilador esta señora es que es
Her son is very good and she can't afford the
muy bueno su hijo y no le llega para el
fan Emilio Hi Emilio baby
ventilador Emilio Hola Emilio nene
bring me the cardboard that I'm going to put bisu
tráeme la cartulina que voy a poner bisu
good chic well I love you very much
bueno chic bueno que te quiero mucho
my set Alfons will you bring me the
sete mío alfons me quieres traer la
cardboard that I'm going to put the bisu that
cartulina que voy a poner el bisu que
reads bua my brother Okay then I
lee la bua mi hermano Bueno pues ya me
almost have to get that lamp  that I
falta menos para para la lámpara esa que
want to buy for the child it
le quiero comprar al niño
's not a normal lamp I
no es una lámpara normal
swear When I show it to you if I can
juro Cuando yo os la enseñe si puedo
reach that budget you can't go
llegar al presupuesto ese no puedes vaya
freak out go freak out but as you said
flipar vaya flipar pero cómo decías tú
Peppa as you said about the people who
Peppa cómo decías tú de la gente que
asked for money for their things come on I'm
pedía dinero para sus cosas vamos Me he
even more freaked out if what
quedado todavía más flipar si lo que
raffi says that he was asking for a
dice raffi que estaba pidiendo por una
jacket that he had seen I can't
chaqueta que había visto no me lo puedo
believe it I already see that as shameless
creer yo ya eso lo veo de poca vergüenza
the truth is I have no reason to say agree
la verdad no tengo que decir acuerdo
We agree I have no
Estamos de acuerdo Yo tengo poca
shame And you too We
vergüenza Y tú también Estamos de
agree man of course for a jacket
acuerdo hombre claro para una chaqueta
not for a fan but it has
no para un ventilador pero que tiene
blades that are not normal ones of course
unas aspas que no son las normales claro
Peppa the same I'm going to ask for the
Peppa lo mismo voy a pedir para la
jacket the same I'm going to ask for the
chaqueta lo mismo voy a pedir para la
jacket how many people are here 25
chaqueta cuánta gente hay aquí 25
people if each of you give away five
personas si cada uno regaláis cinco
members you give me money for the jacket and for
miembro me dais para la chaqueta y para
the trip to Porto to go get the jacket
el viaje a Porto para ir por la chaqueta
what did I just remember pppa climb that
qué me acabo de acordar pppa trepa que a
the jacket costs me money to
mí la chaqueta me cuesta dinero
buy it you have a
comprarla tú las chaquetas tienen un
lot of jackets and you change it every night and it's
montón y te la cambias cada noche y te
free then betrayal at 12:1
sale gratis después traición a las 12:1
I put this first wait You have to
le pongo esto primero espérate Hay que
be  sincere I put the thing about the priest and I
ser sincero le pongo lo del cura y le
say to him There you have it and with me you have
digo Ahí lo tiene y conmigo ya no tienes
nothing more to talk about I put and I put this I
nada que hablar le pongo y le pongo esto
was with Antonio and and and you believe Everything he
estaba con Antonio y y y te crees Todo
tells you tomorrow I'm going to say
lo que te dice él yo mañana voy a decir
everything I said about you Look at you and what about so he was right how
todo lo que decía de ti Fíjate tú y lo
beautiful How
de tan llevaba razón qué bonito Qué
beautiful
bonito
Loli you have plucked yourself you have
Loli te has desplumado tú misma te has
plucked yourself my goodness he is saying to
desplumado madre mía le está diciendo a
Loli he is saying to Loli with all his
Loli le está diciendo a Loli con toda su
face you have plucked yourself you have plucked yourself I
cara tú misma te has desplumado tú misma
wanted to pluck myself my
te has desplumado quería desplumar yo
goodness how
madre
outrageous How outrageous
mía qué barbaridad Qué barbaridad de
really that's what I put on it Elma
verdad eso es lo que yo le pongo elma
she tells me the one who doesn't want to know anything about
ella me dice la que no quiere saber nada
you it's me the one who doesn't want to talk
contigo soy yo la que no quiere hablar
to you anymore you are it's me to you
más contigo eres soy yo a ti
Shameless that's it that was ours
Sinvergüenza ya está eso fue nuestra
our last conversation yes I told him
nuestra última conversación sí le dije
Shameless yes and and
Sinvergüenza sí y y
as if not to
como para no
tell him he was right when I broke
decírselo llevaba razón cuando me he
down that all this comes from breaking down
partido que todo viene esto por partirme
with you to defend what
la cara contigo para defender de lo que
Tania was saying about you that she wanted to
estaba diciendo Tania de ti que quería
close and the whole channel before you went on
cerrar y todo el canal antes de irte de
vacation and  I'll pee crying thinking
vacaciones y mearé de llorar pensando
that you were wrong stop crying
que tú estabas mal dejante de llorar
thinking that you have to say you were
pensando que t tiene que decir t tenía
right Go make a doll and then
razón Vete a hacer muñeca y luego dice
people say that I have to be good
la gente que tenga yo que tener buena
with what well it seems that the climber
con lo que pues parece ser que la trepa
got very angry ah Ah
se enfadó mucho ah Ah
ah This is going to hurt me more than it hurts you
ah Esto me va a doler más a mí que a ti
climber Antonio Tania all the Freaky
trepa Antonio Tania todos los Freaky
tubers This is going to hurt me more than you
tubers Esto me va a doler más que a ti
let's see because you heard an
vamos a ver porque habéis escuchado un
audio right now where the climber tells
audio ahora mismo donde la trepa le dice
Loli Huerta how come Loli
a Loli Huerta que cómo es que la Loli
Huerta thinks of saying that Tania was right
Huerta se le ocurre decir que Tania
let's remember what they
tenía razón vamos a recordar a qué se
meant When I said that Tania was
referían Cuando decía que Tania tenía
right telling the truth with disappointments
razón decir las verdades con decepciones
is that you thought that I was close to
es que os pensabais que yo era íntima de
Peppa Beltrán No I have kept quiet for
Peppa Beltrán No yo me he callado para
Well, I have not wanted to get involved each
Pues bueno no me he querido meter cada
one has their war but when they touch me well I'm
uno tiene su guerra pero cuando me tocan
sorry they find me and that's it
pues lo siento me encuentran y ya está
even if she has said in some live
aunque ella haya dicho en algún directo
that I am her friend I have been
que yo soy su colega Me he quedado
freaking out because I am not friends with
flipando yo porque yo no soy amiga de
pppa Beltrán well that's what it happens when
pppa Beltrán vaya es lo que tiene cuando
the enemy of  my enemy is my friend I
el enemigo de mi enemigo es mi amigo yo
half went to her house I mean I
le me mitado ir hasta su casa o sea yo
see her as a good person and I told her Loli
la veo una buena persona y le dije Loli
don't give a single euro to any channel I
no des ni un euro a ningún canal se lo
told her Loli don't give a single euro to any
dije yo Loli no des ni un euro a ningún
channel and we'll see what happens She told me No
canal y veremos qué pasa Me dijo No
because if not Javiera was right don't give a single
porque si no javiera tenía razón no des
euro let's see what happens but anyway some
ni un euro a ver qué pasa pero bueno un
advice without knowing you You're welcome you'll see how I'm
consejo sin conocerte De nada verás como
going to be right stick around for three months without
voy a tener la razón pégate TR meses sin
donating a single euro to anyone I hope I hope I
donar ni un euro a ninguno Ojalá ojalá
hope that you get the phone I hope it's
ojal que te co el teléfono ojal
heart at that
coraz en ese
moment the true terror
momento el verdadero terror
yoc I have to tell you that a lot of people
yoc te tengo que decir que mucha gente
were right about her a lot of people
tenía razón respecto a ella mucha gente
with time they'll see more things and
con el tiempo se Irán viendo más cosas y
more things will be known but a lot of people
se sabrán más cosas pero mucha gente
I respect her right she's
Tena respeto razón a
completely right but the thing is that there was one
ella toda la razón pero es que había una
thing man there was one thing that nobody
cosa tío había una cosa que es que nadie
remembered to say it man and I'm going to have to
se ha acordado de decirlo tío y lo voy a
say it ok there was one thing
tener que decir yo vale había una cosa
already in which also Nobody remembered
ya en la que también Nadie se acordaba
to say it I could I could get bored eh
de decirlo podría podría aburrirme eh o
I mean Amparo How many times Amparo told me that
sea Amparo Cuántas veces me dijo Amparo
I was in a moment in
que yo que estaba en un momento en
huelva eating a pizza at the olea
huelva comiéndome una pizza en el olea
when I took this screenshot How many times did
cuando saqué esta captura Cuántas veces
the amparo tell me the laetoria climber
me dijo el amparo la trepa laetoria
How many times did he tell me and how many times did they
Cuántas veces me dijo y cuántas veces me
accuse me of falsifying this
acusaron de que yo falsifiqué esta
screenshot How many times did they
captura de pantalla Cuántas veces me lo
tell me I mean I had no other choice but to
dijeron O sea no tenía yo otra cosa que
falsify a
hacer que falsificar una captura de
screenshot to annoy these
pantalla para darle los morros a esta
people but let's listen to this click
gente pero vamos a escuchar este click
that I'm going to put next to see
que os voy a poner a continuación a ver
if they apologize once and for all
si me piden perdón de una [__] vez por
why I have two super Loli chats
qué tengo yo dos super chat de Loli
repeated on screen Hello hello everyone a
repetido en pantalla Hola Hola a todos
thousand kisses Antonio I miss you that
mil besitos Antonio te echo de menos ese
one is
un
curious let's see Antonio I didn't
curiosa hay a ver Antonio que no te
hear you Well I'm going to put it again because I have
escuchado Bien voy a poner otra vez por
two super Loli chats repeated
tengo yo dos super chat de Loli repeti
on screen Hello hello everyone kisses ant I
en pantalla Hola Hola a todos besit ant
miss you it's one and the other the
te echo de menos es uno y el otro el
same one is
mismo se
repeated the most curious thing
repite cosa más curiosa
noat oh very curious the truth is that it has
noat hay curiosísimo la verdad que me ha
caught my attention a lot I will accept
llamado muchísimo la atención aceptaré
your apologies if you
vuestras disculp siis
do Buy her a bottle of water
hacera Comprarle una botella de agua
because we go out and I said I say Look at me
porque salimos y le dije digo Mira mi
for a bottle of water we have with the
para una botella de agua tenemos con el
heat  what are you doing I'm going home
calor que haces me voy para la casa
because I had gone to the ATM I don't know what
porque había ido al cajero no sé qué
something like that you have to have little shame
algo de eso hay que tener poca vergüenza
you and the other one to Troya that what happened last night
tú y la otra a de Troya eso lo de anoche
was and I just found out live I just
fue y me acabo de enterar en directo
found out live this is
acabo de enterar en directo esto es
still later this afternoon but even
todavía después esta tarde pero todavía
later that he just found out
más tarde que se acaba de enterar en
live about ard de Troya's accusation
directo de la acusación de ard de Troya
about the water yesterday ard de Troya took out
de lo del agua ayer ard de Troya sacó
a photo that I sent to the group that
una foto que yo mandé al grupo que
Loli had him and I of one of the
teníamos Loli él y yo de una de las
times that I went out with my mother I just found
veces que salí yo con mi madre acabo de
out live and I would go to the
enterar en directo y iría al
ATM or something to appear at the ATM
cajero o algo para salir en el cajero
I say Look at the heat I'm going through I don't
digo Mira la calo que estoy pasando no
even have enough to buy a bottle of
tengo ni ni para comprar una botella de
water or something like that something something like that something like that
agua o algo de eso algo de eso algo algo
no I
de eso algo de eso algo de eso no yo
sent the photo of my mother there and I said you know I don't
mandé ahí la foto de mi madre y dije
even have enough for water why
tienes se no tengo ni para agua para qué
why would I send that and with what
para qué voy a mandar yo eso y con qué
intention in the group with Loli Huerta
intención en el grupo con Loli Huerta
to inform I did it to inform it's
por informar lo hice por informar es
like a blog that WhatsApp group like
como un blog ese grupo de WhatsApp como
a blog I tell about my day to day life and I
un blog voy contando mi día a día y le
put a  a picture of me and my mom like a
puse una foto mía y de mi madre así un
selfie, let's say he took it, I just
selfie vamos la ha sacado él la acabo yo
posted it now And what he's doing is
de poner ahora Y él lo que hace dar a
implying that I was feeling sorry for
entender que yo me estaba dando pena
Loli so she could see that I didn't even have enough for
para que Loli viera que no tenía ni para
water Who's going to understand that Loli Who's
agua Quién va a entender eso Loli Quién
going to understand that Who was so evil-
va a entender eso Quién ha sido tan mal
minded but let's see if they did it, it was
pensado pero vamos a ver si lo hizo fue
without malice eh you know the other day we
sin maldad eh sabéis que el otro día nos
found out that this gift that
enteramos que este regalo que me
the climber Beltram and Pilar
hicieron la trepa beltram y la Pilar
Ruiz gave me, I just found out a year later
Ruiz me acabo de enterar ahora al año
that the gift that cost 60 was only given to me by
que el regalo que costó 60 solo me lo
Pilar because the climber hasn't
hizo Pilar porque la trepa todavía no le
given her 30 yet, Mario is a gift from
ha dado los 30 el Mario es un regalo de
Peppa and Pily who they told me to
la Peppa y de la pily que me dijeron que
say paypay dig Well then Okay, so I
dijeran paypay dig Bueno pues Vale pues
say paypay I don't know the nonsense because
digo paypay no sé la tontería porque
everyone knows Who they are but it
todo el mundo sabe Quiénes son pero
turns out that what it turns out is that
resulta ser que qué resulta resulta que
well then I get in touch
bueno pues yo ya me pongo en contacto
with Lorena eh I send her 60
con con Lorena eh le mando 60
60 and I say Well between the two of us we'll
60 y digo Pues nada entre las dos lo
do it and she says Pili gave me the money I did
hacemos y dice a mí me dio el dinero la
n't know  that it was a gift
Pili yo no sabía que ese era un regalo
from the climber of course Yes yes I gave it to
de la trepa claro Sí sí yo yo se lo di a
her and Peppa had to pass it on to me
ella y Peppa me lo tenía que pasar a mí
the 30 and what happened No well that it must have been
los 30 y Qué pasó No pues que se habrá
left by the way nothing has arrived to me, she did
quedado por el camino a mí no me ha
n't give you the 30 damn
llegado nada no te dio los 30 [__] yo
now I see that the Mario is not there I say remove
ahora veo que el Mario no está digo quit
the Mario because no No daughter I had it
el Mario porque le no No hija lo tenía
down there I had it up here too for
ahí abajo lo tenía aquí arriba también
a while now it's here on top of the
un tiempo ahora está aquí arriba de la
display case daughter it's here Of course it's
vitrina hija está aquí Claro que está
here where is it going to be and the Mario is
aquí dónde va a estar y el Mario es
entirely mine of course I mean Mario is a
integro mío claro o sea el Mario es un
gift from you in the end it's not a gift from
regalo tuyo al final no es un regalo de
both of us it's from Pip it's from p punto it's from
las dos es de pip es de p punto es de la
Pili of course nothing has arrived to me I would have
Pili claro a m no ha llegado nada se lo
forgotten it It's her condition I mean she's
olvidaría Es que su condición o sea son
30 that's in her you're not going to
30 eso está en ella eso no lo vas a
change that at 70 years old that's her condition
cambiar con 70 años esa es su condición
she's like that [ __ ] How good but I
ella es así [__] Qué bueno pero es que
'm hearing the other one saying that she
estoy oyendo al al otro diciendo que
's still waiting for me to send her the
está esperando todavía que le envíe el
refund for the Jelly Bean he said that he was
reembolso de la Gominola dijo que se lo
going to pay for it How come
iba a pagar Cómo no eso no me lo has
you haven't ever told me that about the Mario yeah yeah I
dicho tú nunca lo del Mario ya ya ya lo
know yeah Well  yes well well anyway Hey I just
sé ya Pues sí pues bueno igual Oye me he
got here for Christmas but
llegado ahora para navidad pero es que
her condition must not be that bad it must not be that
su condición no debe pico quilla no debe
bad everywhere you for her to
pico por todos lados tú para que me
give me money I say I know can the
diera dinero digo yo se puede ser la
other one be more vile than that that more vile you can't
otra más ruin que eso eso más ruin ya no
be anything more vile no Tell me can you
se puede ser nada más ruin no Dime se
be more vile than that but eh Rubin
puede ser más ruin que eso pero eh Rubín
and stupid because How many times have we said
y tonto porque Cuántas veces hemos dicho
that here Loli has offered us eh to put
que aquí Loli nos ha ofrecio eh poner
a caregiver for Agustinita and
una cuidadora para la agustinita y
How many times has she offered money and we have
Cuántas veces ha ofrecio dinero y le
told her no it's that it's nonsense What
hemos dicho que no es que es tontería Lo
happens is that of course she plays with
que pasa que claro juega con con la
uncertainty And that Then she plays with
incertidumbre Y eso Entonces juega con
that And you know what she plays with with
con eso Y sabes con qué juega con la
people's sensitivity yes yes yes yes
sensibilidad de las personas sí sí sí sí
but with evil to the maximum evil I
pero a la maldad a la maldad máxima O
mean let's see if I understand Let's see if I
sea a ver si yo entiendo A ver si yo
understand one thing who plays with
entiendo una cosa quién juega con la
people's sensitivity the one who
sensibilidad de las personas el que
collects 240 bucks and forgets
recolecta 240 pavos y se le olvida
for 6 months or the one who tells What
durante 6 meses o el que cuenta Lo que
she has done in a WhatsApp group and I
ella ha hecho en un grupo de WhatsApp y
repeat it again that she has
vuelvo a repetirlo que otra vez ha
said again that she just found out
vuelto a decir que se acaba de enterar
but on December 7th there was already
pero el 7 de diciembre ya había
answered you won't have made up a
contestado no se habrá inventado una
lie Look, I'm here for a bottle of
mentira Mirad vengo para una botella de
water, eh today they brought like two boxes of
agua eh hoy han traído como dos cajas
meat weapons Ah I have some water, I have two
arma carne Ah tengo para agua tengo dos
boxes, well, Two more, Two climbers That's 240 plus
cajas pues Dos más Dos trepa Son 240 más
the visum plus the 30 battery when you
los visum más los 30 de pila cuando tú
can, no rush, okay, I'm tired of
puedas sin prisa vale estoy harto de
repeating it and I don't know how many times I'll have to
repetirlo y no sé cuántas veces lo
repeat it throughout
tendré que repetir a lo largo de de de
this journey on YouTube, but the time it
esta andadura de de YouTube pero la vez
is Well, I'll repeat it if my mother
de que sea Pues lo repetiré si mi madre
had wanted civil money, she would have
hubiera querido dinero civilino primero
set up Tele5 first and made up
se hubiera montado tele5 y se hubiera
all the things If she's so
inventado todas las cosas Si es tan
sly and so climber and so snake-like like
sibilina y tan trepa y tan culebra como
you guys say on Tele5, she would have
ustedes decir en tele5 se hubiera
made up a thousand things when she left
inventado mil cosas cuando salió del
Big Brother to show the calls
gran hermano para que ponga las llamadas
from when you and I don't talk, give me
desde cuando tú y yo no hablamos me da
permission to show the calls from
permiso para que ponga las llamadas de
when she and I don't talk, permission
cuando ella y yo no hablamos permiso
for her conversations, putting
para las conversaciones de ella poniendo
Loli down saying that she's going to fleece her, they
verde a la Loli diciendo que la va
didn't give it to me, they
desplumar ese no me daba se lo
offered it to her, imagine what would have happened if she
ofrecieron imaginarse lo que hubiera si
were that person that you wrote that
fuera esa persona que usted escribí ese
profile of a person on T5, she would have had a
perfil de persona en t5 hubiera hecho
drink making things up, I hope
trago inventándose cosas Espero que
you're up to date  parrot of these of these
estéis al loro de estos de estos
messages and directly them and
mensajes y directamente los
she for money for a lot of money that
y ella por dinero por mucho dinero que
was offered to her she chose to say No if she
se le ofrecieron optó por decir No si
were that type of person she would have been
fuera ese perfil de persona hubiera lo
able to do it I just found out
hubiera podido hacer me acabo de enterar
live think a little about that
en directo pensa un poquito en eso que
Loli and all the things that she has
Loli y todas las cosas que le ha
offered him that he has returned the 500 and
ofrecido que le ha devuelto los 500 y lo
what T was right how beautiful How beautiful
de T llevaba razón qué bonito Qué bonito
Loli you have plucked yourself you have
Loli te has desplumado tú misma te has
plucked my mother you have
desplumado madre mía tú misma te has
plucked yourself I wanted to pluck myself but we are we are
desplumado quería desplumar yo pero
talking about the same
estamos estamos hablando de la misma
person it really shocks me me
persona es que de verdad me choca a mí
that as I know her r person my
yo que como la conozco r persona mi
family has always been solid My mother
familia siempre ha sido solid Mi madre
is that she has been giving and
es que se ha estado de de dar y de
offering and to the people who
ofrecer y de a la gente que le hacía
needed it She has always been helping her
falta Siempre le ha estado ayudando
because what she was waiting for is to
porque ella lo que estaba esperando es a
see if in some way she could change
ver si de alguna forma se podía cambiar
that date And show it that Monday and she had
esa fecha Y enseñarlo ese lunes y lo
done it that Monday and I know who
había hecho ese lunes y yo lo sé quién
For whom financially with help with
Por quién económicamente con ayuda con
food with things with clothes with taking it to a
comida con cosas con ropa con llevarlo a
place with helping him with the move with
sitio con ayudarlo con la mudanza con
anything that anything from
cualquier cosa que cualquier cosa de
all of life even made a Barriada eh
toda la vida hasta hecho una Barriada eh
Until this neighborhood association
Hasta cuando estab asociación de vecinos
was the president and the president
era la presidenta y estaba la presidenta
of the neighborhood associations was Deira and she
de las asociaciones de vecinos deira y
was helping each association, it
estaba ayudando a cada asociación
turns out that Peppa asked that this
resulta que Peppa pedido que esa
donation not be public so that the
donación no sea pública que la
association could not say whether she had donated or
asociación no pueda decir si ha donado o
not and she asked her to sign a paper for
no y le ha pedido firmado un papel para
that and the girl from the association told her
eso y la chica de la asociación le ha
that it could not be done. She
dicho que eso no se puede hacer quería
wanted it to be anonymous, that is,
quería que fuera anónima o sea quería
she wanted the receipt, not the proof of
ella el el recibo no el justificante de
having donated, but that it should not be public,
haber donado pero que no fuera público
I imagine so that the date could not be seen.
me imagino para que no se viera la fecha
Indeed, you cannot even imagine
no Efectivamente es que ni os imagináis
the thing that you have not
la de cosa que ustedes como no la habéis
experienced, but it is worth applauding the
vivido pero es para aplaudir la
[Music]
[Música]
s
s